[
{"question":"1. Group index of soil ranges such that",
"answers":{
            "a":"0 < GI < 20",
            "b":"0 <= GI <=20",
            "c":"0 <= GI <=25",
            "d":"0 < GI < ¡Þ"
          },
"correctAnswer":"b"},

{"question":"2. The IS classification of soils is",
"answers":{
            "a":"Particles size classification",
            "b":"Textural classification",
            "c":"Highway research board classification",
            "d":"Modified unified classification"
          },
"correctAnswer":"d"},

{"question":"3. The biggest size of clay particles is",
"answers":{
            "a":"0.0002mm ",
            "b":"0.002mm",
            "c":" 0.02mm",
            "d":"0.075mm"
          },
"correctAnswer":"b"},

{"question":"4. The maximum size of fine grained soil is",
"answers":{
            "a":"0.002mm",
            "b":"0.075mm",
            "c":"0.75mm",
            "d":"4.75mm"
          },
"correctAnswer":"b"},

{"question":"5. Stokes law is valid only if the size of particle is",
"answers":{
            "a":"< 0.0002mm",
            "b":" > 0.2mm",
            "c":"Between 0.2mm and 0.0002mm ",
            "d":"All of the above"
          },
"correctAnswer":"c"},

{"question":"6. Which of the following is a measure of particle size range",
"answers":{
            "a":"Effective size ",
            "b":"Uniformity coefficient",
            "c":"Coefficient of curvature",
            "d":"None of the above"
          },
"correctAnswer":"b"},

{"question":"7. Uniformity coefficient of soil is",
"answers":{
            "a":"<1 ",
            "b":"=1 ",
            "c":">1",
            "d":"<=1"
          },
"correctAnswer":"d"},

{"question":"8. Sieve analysis is used when size of particle is",
"answers":{
            "a":"> 0.075mm",
            "b":"< 0.075mm",
            "c":"4.75mm",
            "d":"0.01mm"
          },
"correctAnswer":"a"},

{"question":"9. Sedimentation analysis is used when size of particle is",
"answers":{
            "a":"> 0.75mm",
            "b":"< 0.075mm",
            "c":"4.75mm",
            "d":"0.01mm "
          },
"correctAnswer":"b"},

{"question":"10. A flat grain size distribution curve shows a",
"answers":{
            "a":"Narrow range of grain size",
            "b":"Wide range of grain size",
            "c":"Uniform grain size",
            "d":"Grain size from two representative fractions"
          },
"correctAnswer":"b"}

]
